菲比  你还在等待接通吗
Phoebe, Are you still on hold?
我两小时前就该打给我爸了
I was supposed to call my Dad back like two hours ago.
有  他插播过
Oh, yeah. He clicked on.
他说等你能打给他时就打过去
He said call him as soon as you get a chance.
他在那啥啥地方
He's at Flimbees.
那啥啥是哪儿
What's Flimbees?
我记不起正确说法时都这么说
That's the word I use when I can't remember the real thing.
好吧  挂电话  真是够了
Okay, hang up! That's it. Come on!
不要  瑞秋  他们就是要我放弃
No. Rachel. That's what they want me to do.
我的保修卡明天就过期了
My warranty expires tomorrow.
如果我一直打不通...
If I don't get through...
就不会有人免费修理我的破电话
...they won't fix my crappy, broken phone for free!
我们不能让他们得逞  这是我们与他们的较量
We cannot let them win! It's us versus them!
没错
Yes!
我得再问一次晚上的票  你们要几张
Listen, I gotta double-check for tickets tonight. Who got what?
我要一张
I have one.
我要两张  我要带彼特去
I need two. I'm bringing Pete.
我的男朋友
My boyfriend.
我有男朋友了
I have a boyfriend now.
你两张  罗斯  你呢
Two it is. Ross. How about you?
那好  我也要两张
Yeah, I also need two.
真的吗  第二个人是谁
Really? Who's number two?
第二个人是谁
Whose Number Two?
这是下水道工人的高难度游戏之一啊
One of the more difficult games sewer workers play.
就是有一个人嘛
No, it's just this person.
是约会对象吗
Like a date-type person?
算是吧  是工作上认识的女生
Yeah, kind of. It's this woman from work.
希望不会太奇怪  会吗  瑞秋
I hope that won't be too weird. Will it, Rach?
不  一点也不会
No. Not at all.
其实我也要带人去
I was actually gonna bring someone myself.
但是你只要一张票
But you said one ticket.
我是说我再多一张
I meant me plus one.
好  还有谁是多一张的
Okay. Did you guys mean you plus one?
-好  晚上见  -好
- All right. I'll see you tonight. - Okay.
-好  再见  -再见
- Okay. Bye-bye. - Bye
拜拜
Bye-bye.
我得找个男伴
Okay, I need a date!
对了  你们终于要见到凯特了
Oh, hey! You guys are finally gonna get to meet Kate!
我借了点你的古龙水擦  希望她会喜欢
And I borrowed some of your cologne. I hope she likes it.
乔伊  你这是干嘛
Joey. What are you doing?
你俩没戏的  她已经有别人了
That's never gonna happen. She's seeing somebody.
对  而且我没有古龙水
Yeah, and I don't have any cologne.
刮胡膏旁边那个绿瓶
Green bottle next to the shaving cream.
那是鸭子的除虫药
Oh. Worm medicine for the duck.
-拿去  这件给你穿  -谢谢  好的
- Here you go. You can wear this. - Thanks. Okay.
我把电话放下
I'm setting the phone down.
但是我人还在
But I'm still here.
不要走开  我还在
Just don't go anywhere. I'm still here.
不要转线  我就在这里
Don't switch or anything, because I'm right here.
等我一下下
Just one sec.
等一下  一下下
One sec. One second!
等等  一下就好...
Wait! One second! Just....
-菲比  -干嘛  莫妮卡  我好害怕
-Phoebe? - What? Monica, I'm scared!
拜托  亲爱的  那是袖子
All right. Honey, that's-that's a sleeve. Okay?
而且我们可以开免提
And we also have a speakerphone.
请不要挂断
Please stay on the line.
我们很重视您的来电
Your call is important to us.
好了  你得挂断  因为我们要迟到了
Okay, wait, you gotta hang up 'cause we're gonna be late.
谢谢您的等候  接下来将为您服务
Thank you for your patience. You're the next caller.
漂亮  我是下一个
Yes! Yes! I'm the next caller!
你居然还叫我挂掉
You were gonna have me hang up.
你说能带鸡和鸭去剧院吗
Can you take a duck and a chick to the theater?
-当然不行  -好的
- Of course not. - Okay.
我只是想让别人告诉它们
I just wanted them to hear it from somebody else.
-嗨  瑞秋  -嗨  你好吗
- Hi, Rach. - Oh, hi, how are you?
很好
Good.
-看来我们是最早到  -看样子是的
- Looks like we're the first ones here. - Yeah, looks that way.
拔得头筹
First ones here!
汤米  这是罗斯  罗斯  这是汤米
Oh, Tommy, this is Ross. Ross, this is Tommy.
抱歉  这是凯琳  凯琳  这是...
Oh, I'm sorry. This is Cailin. Cailin, this is...
对不起
Sorry.
放开
And break!
好的
OKay.
-我要去一趟洗手间  -好的
- I think I'm gonna run to the ladies' room. - Okay.
-我跟你去  -我去找座位
- I'll join you. - I'll get our seats.
这真是...
So...well, this is...uh,
-有点尴尬  -为何
- This is awkward. - Yeah?
因为瑞秋和我交往过
Well, because Rachel and l used to go out.
我不知道
Oh, I didn't know that.
那这才叫尴尬
Well, then this is awkward.
-座位是...   -应该是这里
- So what do you...? - I think we're here.
打扰一下  对不起
Uh, huh. Excuse me, I'm sorry,
你们好像坐到我们的位子了
I-Ithink you may be in our seats.
应该没有吧
No, I don't think so.
-可以看一下你的票吗  -当然可以
- Could we take a look at your ticket? - Sure.
没错  你看  上面写着"D排13号"
Yeah. Yeah, see, this says,"D-13"....
-这样啊  我还以为...  -你还以为
-Oh, well, I thought that... - Oh, you thought, huh?
你以为也没有用  你俩老白痴
Yeah, well that didn't really work out too well for you did you idiot!!
你们是猪头吗
What are you, a moron?
上面印着D排13号  好吗
It says, "D-13"! Okay?
看看四周  你被双数包围了
Look, you're surrounded by even numbers!
这还不够明显吗
Does that give you a clue?
-引座员让我们坐得  -引座员当然对喽
- Uh, the usher told us to come? - Oh! Oh! The usher must be right!
他真是白受了那么多训练  滚
What, with all that training they go through! Get out!!
拿去
Here!
-兄弟  你要靠走道吗  -不用了
- Hey, man, you want the aisle? - No, I'm good.
-他来了  -我们的大明星到了
- There he is! - There's our star!
你演得好棒
You were great!
那么  你们觉得怎样
So? What'd you think?
跟两裸女坐翘翘板那出有得拼
Almost as good as the play with the two naked girls on the seesaw.
-我没有演那出  -我知道
- I wasn't in that. - I know.
来见一下大家  各位  她是凯特
Listen, I want you to meet everybody. Everybody, this is Kate.
借过  借过  亲爱的
Excuse me. Excuse me. Sweetheart!
过来
Come!
那就是你心上人
So that's the girl you like.
我跟你说  瑞秋的男伴是神经病
I tell you, this guy Rachel is with is crazy, okay?
他对陌生人大吼大叫  我觉得他很糟糕
He viciously screamed at total strangers. I think he's bad news.
慢着  你不喜欢瑞秋约会的对象吗
Wait a minute, wait a minute. You don't like the guy Rachel's dating?
真奇怪啊
Well, that's odd.
萝伦  各位  这是凯特的替角萝伦
Oh, hey, Lauren. You guys, this is Kate's understudy, Lauren.
-天啊  你好面熟  -对啊
- Hey, gosh, you look so familiar. - Oh, yeah.
我们在你那栋楼的走廊上见过
I ran into you in the hallway in your building.
就在我跟乔伊上床之后
It was right after I slept with Joey.
他第二天就甩了我
He dumped me the next day.
你们是怎么认识的
So how'd you guys meet?
简单的说  我追了她几个月
Well ah, the short version is, I ah pursued her for a couple of months,
然后给她一张两万元支票  她就成了我女朋友了
Then I gave her a check for $20,000 and she was mine.
没错  复杂的说
Yeah. In the long version,
我会因为他光说简单的  抛弃了他
I dump him for telling people the short version.
乔伊  小宝贝  你太棒了
Joey, sweetheart, you were fabulous!
各位  这是我的经纪人艾丝特尔
You guys, this is my agent, Estelle.
你们好
How do you do?
这两个姑娘演得太出色了
Oh, you two girls were outstanding!
她们有经纪人吗
Do they have representation?
她们没有参演
They weren't in the play.
我们不是演员
We're not actors.
真可惜
What a shame!
她的脸蛋加上她的胸部
With her face and her chest,
我可以弄出个尤物来
I could really put something together.
可以借我吗
Could I borrow it?
你好  记得我吗
Hi. Remember me?
当然
Hi. Yeah.
汤米在排队上厕所
Tommy's in line for the bathroom...
有人插队  我觉得他要抓狂了
...and someone just cut. I think he's gonna snap.
罗斯  我要走了
Ross, I'm gonna go.
走  为什么
Go? Why?
不知道  或许是因为...
I don't know. Could be because I don't feel like...
我不想整晚等着看一个人会不会发疯
standing around all night waitingfor some guy who may or may not scream.
凯琳  他绝对会发疯
Cailin, he definitely will scream.
-再见  罗斯  -再见
- Goodbye, Ross. - Uh, oh-ho bye.
各位  剧评来了
Here we go, people!
"节礼日"
"Boxing Day.
"露西儿洛泰尔剧院"  一堆废话
The Lucille Lortel Theatre, blah-la-la-la?
乔伊·崔比安尼
Joey Tribbiani
表演不够稳定
gives an uneven performance.
不过崔比安尼还不是这出戏最差的一环
But Mr. Tribbiani is not the worst thing in this production."
帅
Yes!
凯特·米勒差劲做作的诠释实在可笑
"Kate Miller's awkward and mannered portrayal is laughable."
又一堆废话
Badda-badda-badda.
来了  导演部份
Here it is! "The direction...
马歇尔·汤恩导演...
... by Marshall Townend is...."
谢谢各位演员
Thank you, boys and girls.
你们毁了我的一生
You've ruined my life.
请用我妈做的蟹饼
Please stuff your talentless faces...
填满你们没有才华的脸蛋
...with my mother's crab cakes!
借过
Excuse me!
没人介意我保留这个吧
Does anyone mind if I save this?
-戏演完了吗  -是啊  你去哪里了
- Is the play over? - Yeah, where were you?
谢谢您的等候  接下来将为您服务
Thank you for your patience. You're the next caller.
五个小时前就说要为您服务了
You were the next caller five hours ago.
你一定快疯了
You must be going crazy.
没有哦  我也没闲着
Nah. I kept myself busy.
对了  我把你们房里的东西对调了
Okay, yeah, I put your stuff in her room and her stuff in your room.
你还好吗
You okay?
好极了
Fabulous.
听着  那些剧评家
Listen, drama critics, they're nothing but,
只是当不成演员的人
but people who couldn't make it as actors.
-你知道你该怎么做吗  -去当剧评家
- You know what you should do? - Become a drama critic.
我受伤了
I am hurt!
祝你们两家
A plague...
遭蝗虫瘟疫之灾
...on both your houses!
对了  他看完剧评之后甩了我
By the way, he dumped me tonight after he read my review.
-真过份  -是啊
- Oh, classy. - Yep.
我还真有眼光
I sure know how to pick them.
我为了这出戏放弃一出连续剧
You know I gave up a part on a soap for this?
我也放弃了一份工作
Wow! Yeah I ah, I gave up a job too.
-是吗  什么工作  -替猫咪剪指甲
- Really? What? - Declawing cats.
这样吧  我陪你走回家
Hey, tell you what, let me walk you home.
我们在每个报摊停下
We'll stop by every newsstand
烧掉所有的时报和邮报
and burn every copy of The Times and The Post.
-为什么要烧邮报  -你没看邮报吗
- Why The Post?. - You didn't see The Post?.
-没有  你看了吗  -没有  怎么了
- No. You? - No. Why?
你真觉得那些剧评家是因为嫉妒我
You really think these newspapers are just jealous of me?
绝对的  你有才华  长得又美
Absolutely. You're talented and you're good-looking.
你人好又可爱
You're sweet and cute.
我知道  所以他们才攻击我
I know. That's why they trashed me.
-慢着  等一下  -怎么了
- Wait. Wait a minute. - What?
我实在搞不懂你
I don't get you.
你先是讨厌我
I mean, first you hate me.
然后跟我上床
Then you sleep with me.
然后你又跟我撇清关系  现在又想要我了
Then you want nothing to do with me. Now you want me again?
干嘛  难道你没跟女演员约过会吗
What? So you never went out with an actress before?
凯特  你喜欢我吗
Kate, do you even like me?
-当然喜欢  -那你为什么拒绝我
-Of course I do. - So how come you blew me off?
-为什么要跟他在一起  -我不知道
- I mean, how come you were with him? - I don't know.
我就是这样
I just do this.
我总是要挑  挑那个最聪明的...
I always have to pick, like, the smartest guy...
或挑那个最有才华的
...or the most talented guy.
我为什么就不能挑一个你这样的呢
Why can't I just pick someone like you?
谢了
Thanks.
你懂我的意思
You know what I mean.
我是说最体贴的人
I mean, like, the sweetest guy.
乔伊  你真的好...
Joey. You're just so....
你好...
You're so...
好...
...so....
好吧  真是拿你没办法
Okay, okay, hey.
来  把你的脚抬上来
Here we go. Let's get your feet up there.
晚安  凯特
Good night. Kate.
祝你好梦
Sweet dreams.
我把桶放在这里  免得你想倒苦水
I'm gonna put this can right here in case you have to hurl.
请不要挂断  我们很重视您的来电
Please stay on the line. Your call is very important to us.
菲比  你已经24小时没睡了  去睡吧
Pheebs. You've been up for 24 hours. Go to sleep.
亲爱的  这样有损健康
Honey. Th-this isn't healthy.
不  我很好
No, no, I'm fine.
你知道为什么吗  因为我吃了核黄素
And you know why? Because of all the riboflavin.
-这不还是昨晚那套衣服吗  -对
- Didn't you have that on last night? - Yeah.
我在凯特家过夜  但是什么也没做
I stayed at Kate's but nothing happened.
菲比  你怎么没来
Hey, Pheebs, where were you?
我很抱歉  乔伊
I'm so, so sorry Joey.
我一定会去看你演的戏
I am definitely gonna see your play.
你的戏对我们很重要
I swear, your play is very important to us.
谢谢你的耐心等候
Thank you for your patience.
我很快就会去看你的戏
Your play is the next play I'm gonna see.
你跟凯特怎么样
Anyway, how did it go with Kate?
感觉好棒
Oh, it was great!
我陪她走回家
Yeah, I-I walked her home,
我们之间心有灵犀的感觉这棒
and it was amazing how much weconnected, y'know?
然后她昏了过去
Then ah, then she passed out,
后来她又醒了过来
but then she woke up. Yeah?
我们聊了一整晚
And we stayed up all night talking,
现在我们彻底为彼此疯狂
and now we're like totally crazy about each other!
-乔伊  你经历了"关键性的一晚"  -什么
-Joey, you had "the night"! - What?
当两个人发现他们坠入爱河时
When two people realize their feelings for each other...
他们会聊上很久  了解对方的一切
...and they talk for hours and learn all about the other person.
是吗
You think?
-你了解她的家人吗  -两个兄弟  一个死了
- Did you learn about her family? - Two brothers. One died!
漂亮
Yes!
这是吧台那位女士请的
This is from the woman at the bar.
对不起  她认错人了
Sorry. She thought you were somebody else.
-现在几点  -一点
- What time is it? - One.
7点15分
7:15.
我的表坏了
Watch doesn't work.
汤米快来了  我们要去吃饭
Tommy's supposed to be here soon. We're going to lunch.
听着  我本来不想说的  但是...
Look, I wasn't gonna say anything to you, but....
好吧  我觉得你不该跟汤米来往
All right, I don't think you should be seeing Tommy anymore.
-是吗  -是啊
- You don't? - No.
那家伙很恶劣  非常恶劣
The guy is mean. I mean, really mean.
我觉得你应该离他远一点
I think you should stay away from him.
-或许我应该离所有男人远一点  -不是这样
- Or maybe I should stay away from all men. - No.
我不只是在嫉妒
It's not just because I'm jealous.
我是说  我不是在嫉妒  知道吗
I mean, I'm not. I'm not jealous. Okay? It's...
那家伙是个疯子
Look, the guy, he screamed,
他冲着对坐错位子的夫妇大吼大叫
he actually screamed at this couple sitting in our seats.
对啊  落幕的时候
Yeah, and at the end of the play...
他还站起来
...he got up, you know?
然后开始用力拍打他的双手
and he just started, like, banging his hands together.
好  你们不信就算了
Fine, you don't want to believe me, that's fine.
-没关系   -我们开玩笑的
- No, that's fine. - We're kidding.
-罗斯  罗斯  -别这样
- Ross, Ross. - Come on.
没有人相信我  你们当都我在耍宝
No one believe me. I'm Mr. Funny to you. Mr. Funny!
对不起  汤米
Sorry, Tommy.
杯子里是什么  罗斯
What's in the cup, Ross?
杯子里是什么
What is in the cup?
好吧  是咖啡
Okay, it's coffee.
冰咖啡吗  请告诉我是冰咖啡
Iced coffee? Tell me it's iced coffee.
-是热...  -热咖啡
- It's hot - Hot coffee!
你这个白痴  你想拿热咖啡泼我  是吧
You idiot! You gonna spill hot coffee all over me,huh?
你怎么回事  你是剪着
What are you? Just a big, stupid
白痴发型的大白痴吗
doofy idiot with a doofy idiot hairdo?
你最喜欢夏天的什么
What's your favorite thing about summertime?
-去海边玩  看天色很晚才变暗  -不错
- Going to the beach when it stays light real late. - Yeah.
亲爱的
HOney.
你最喜欢夏天的什么
Say what's your favorite thing about summer?
不知道  新剪过的草地的味道吧
I don't know. Probably the smell of freshly cut grass.
-这个好  -对啊
- That's a good one. - Yeah.
抱歉  抱歉  我迟到了
Sorry! Sorry, I'm late; sorry, I'm late!
我家阿鸡阿鸭吵架  场面很乱
My duck and my chick had a fight. It was ugly.
伙计  我们等着你  上场吧
Look, we held the curtain for you buddy. Come on, let's go!
-快点  -好的
- Let's go!  - Okay.
维克  你上哪去了  宝贝
Vic! Where have you been, baby?
凯特呢
Where's Kate?
-她在洛杉矶找到工作  -什么
- She got a job in L.A. - What?
我等了你一整夜  你上哪去了
I've been waiting up all night for you. Where have you been?
你上哪去了  维克
Where have you been, Vic?
去窗子旁边
Go to the window.
我去车上拿个东西给你看
I wanna run down to the truck and show you something.
你要给我看什么  维克
What do you got down there, Vic?
帆布底下藏了什么
What do you got under that tarp?
她什么时候走
When is she leaving?
今晚  你在干什么
Tonight. What are you doing?
我马上上来
I'm coming up!
可以借用下电话吗
Hey, you mind if I use the phone?
你何不去对面用我们的  因为她...
Why don't you use ours across the hall, because she...
-有点问题  -谢谢
- ... has problems. - Thanks.
汤米  对不起
Sorry, Tommy.
我差点把热咖啡泼到你身上
I almost spilled this hot coffee on you.
是啊  但是你没有
Yeah, but you didn't.
没错  但是...
No, but...
这是热的
...it's hot.
罗斯  别闹了  我们都看腻了
Ross. Would you stop it? It's getting really old.
真不敢相信居然没有人相信我
I can't believe no one believes me.
我相信你
I do. I believe you.
真的吗  菲比
You do, Pheebs?
对  但是我也相信她说我是下一个
Yeah. But I also believed her when she said I was next.
嗨  小东西
Hey there, little fella.
毛毛脸  你好吗
Mr. Fuzzy Man, how you doing?
恶心死了
Gross!
白痴
Idiot!
白痴黄毛鸡
Stupid, little, fuzzy, yellow creature!
"你看我  我好可爱  我是恶心的小鸡"
"Oh, look at me! I'm so cute! I'm a little chick who's disgusting!"
天啊  你这种笨蛋  怎么还没绝种
God, you're so stupid, how are you not yet extinct!!
你叫什么叫
What are you quacking about?
白痴唐老鸭
Dumb Donald Dodo!
离阿鸭远一点
Step away from the duck.
很抱歉  小鸡鸡
Sorry, little Mr. Chickadee.
谁叫你在我手上拉屎
Sorry you went doody in my hand!
看来我们是没希望了
Well I guess we're not going out anymore.
妈的
Man!
乔伊  幸好赶上了  我一直找不到你
Joey, I'm so glad I caught you. I couldn't find you before.
发生什么事了  为什么要去洛杉矶
Wh-wh-what's going on? Wh-what's this about L.A.?
《综合医院》还是要我出演
They still want me for General Hospital.
但是...
But...
那我们呢
...what about us?
昨晚感觉很棒
Last night was wonderful.
但我不能为了你留下来
But I can't stay here just for you.
那就为了博物馆留下来
So stay for the museums.
-对不起  -乔伊上场
- I'm sorry. - Joey, on-stage!
至少等到落幕再走  可以吗
Well can you at least stay to the end of the play?
我陪你去机场  我想跟你道别
I'll go to the airport with you. I want to say goodbye.
维克  你在哪里
Where are you,Vic?
一小时后的班机  我得走了
Flight's in an hour. I gotta go.
维克
Vic?
-维克  -等一下
- Vic! - In a minute!
就这样了吗  维克多
So this is it, Victor?
我想是的
Yeah. I guess it is.
听我说
Listen...
我要说再见了  我会长话短说
... I gotta say goodbye, and I gotta say it quick
因为我的心好痛
because this is killing me.
我要你知道  我永远不会忘记你
One thing you gotta know is that I will never forget you.
但是你有你该做的事
But you got things you have to do now.
而我也是
And so do l.
所以......
And so...
我要登上太空船
... I'm gonna get on this spaceship...
前往布拉刚7号星寻找替代燃料
...and I'm gonna go to Blaargon-7 in search of alternative fuels.
等我两百年后回来
But when I return 200 years from now...
你早就不在人世了
...you'll be long gone...
而我却一点也不会老
... but I won't have aged at all.
所以请告诉你的曾曾孙女
So you tell your great, great granddaughter...
叫她找我
...to look me up.
因为  爱德莉安
Because, Adrianne...
亲爱的......
... baby...
我想见见她
... I'm gonna want to meet her.
别了  维克
So long, Vic!
菲比  已经两天了
Phoebe. It's been two days.
我知道
Yeah, I know.
幸好是801免付费电话
Good thing it's one of those 801 numbers, right?
菲比  800才是免付费电话  801是犹他州码
Phoebe, 800 is toll free. 801 is Utah.
不  不  不可能
No, no, no, oh no-no-no,
一定是800  大公司都有免付费专线
It has to be 800 because all those big companies have 800 numbers.
每个......
Every....
犹他州大公司都是801开头
Yeah, every big Utah-based company has one.
-菲比  -真的很抱歉  我会付钱的
- Phoebe! - Sorry. I'm so sorry. I will pay you back.
她还是不挂电话
And yet she's still not hanging up the phone.
-挂掉啦  -快挂掉
- Hang up! - Hang up the phone!
好啦
Fine! Fine!
怎么了
What?
我好像把它摔坏了
Well, I think I broke it.
没关系  你们可以打这个电话号码
But that's all right. Here's the number where you can call.